https://ceramicartsnetwork.org/privacy-policy/

Data Collection
When you register for Ceramic Arts Network, we collect only your name and email address. This information is used to personalize the site and to verify the member status of certain registered users. Registration is not required to browse the site.
We also log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which parts of Ceramic Arts Network you visit and how much time you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable. The only other information automatically provided to us is the type of computer and operating system you are using. Your browser supplies us with this information.
Like many websites, Ceramic Arts Network uses cookies to help us personalize your browsing experience and to collect information about how you use the site.
Your email address may be used for weekly newsletter distribution and certain marketing emails sent by The American Ceramic Society (owner of the CeramicArtsNetwork.org), and its commercial vendors. You will always be provided with an option to opt out of any email distributions.
Data Security
The American Ceramic Society is fully committed to data security. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide to us online. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us. In this regard, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data while you are on the Internet. At a minimum, we encourage you to change your passwords often, using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure that you are using a secure browser as you surf the Internet.
Commitment to Privacy
The American Ceramic Society is actively committed to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce. If you have a question specific to privacy, please contact us at editor@ceramicartsdaily.org. If we decide to change our privacy policy, those changes will be posted on this page.
California Privacy Rights
Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who are registered users of CeramicArtsNetwork.org and non-registered users of CeramicArtsNetwork.org who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from CeramicArtsNetwork.org, once a calendar year, information about the personal information it shared, if any, with other businesses for marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of personal information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which CeramicArtsNetwork.org shared such personal information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2018 will receive information about 2017).
European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
This section applies if you are an individual located in the European Union (“EU”). Subject to applicable law, you have rights in relation to your Personal Data:
Right of access: If you ask us, we will confirm whether we are processing your Personal Data and, if so, provide you with a copy of that Personal Data (along with certain other details). If you require additional copies, we may need to charge a reasonable fee.
Right to rectification: If your Personal Data is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to have it rectified or completed.
Right to erasure: You may ask us to delete or remove your Personal Data and we will do so in some circumstances, such as where we no longer need it (we may not delete your data when other interests outweigh your right to deletion).
Right to data portability: You have the right to obtain your Personal Data from us that you consented to give us or that is necessary to perform a contract with you. We will give you your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. You may reuse it elsewhere.
To obtain your information please send your request to:
Remember MeThis setting should only be used on your home or work computer.
Lost your password? Create New Password
No password? Sign up
×
×
